blogtobollywood.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or comment on our posts.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

– To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s system to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding of our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we use Advertisements ?**

Yes, We are currently involved with following vendors for displaying ads on our website:  
1)Google(www.google.com)

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.  
Else you can visit AboutAds(aboutads.info) for opting out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://blogtobollywood.com](http://blogtobollywood.com/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://blogtobollywood.com/privacy-policy/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below address or email.

www.blogtobollywood.com  
BlogtoBollywood,  
1304 Block B,  
Jaipuriya Sunrise Greens,  
Indirapuram,  
Ghaziabad -201014  
email : feedback@blogtobollywood.com
